Mark Wood – .Net developer and Tester

Professional Summary

Lightning-fast, exacting .NET developer with 2+ years of experience. Skilled in ASP.NET MVC, and client-side web development. Seeking position at Citrix. As intern at BrainWild Global, worked on 10+ projects for SQL database design. Developed and maintained over 20 .NET websites with 100% client satisfaction. Also experienced in manual and automation testing.

Work Experience

.NET Developer Intern

BrainWild Global

Nov 2017-March 2019

- Worked in an Agile team of .NET developers for a fast-paced software development firm.
- Implemented a smoothing function into a client CAD tool that improved UX scores 25%.
- Worked on 10+ SQL database design projects. Improved speed to complete projects by 35% in 15 weeks.
- Developed and provided maintenance for 20+ .NET websites, using ASP.NET MVC, jQuery,
 HTML, and CSS. Achieved 100% client satisfaction and on-time completion.
- Created remote coding and testing environment with bash and Docker scripts.

Freelance .NET Developer

June 2016-Nov 2017

- Created five real-world eCommerce websites for various clients. One said, "You've increased my revenue by 50% overnight."
- Created an iOS notes app that uses persistent data storage to archive notes. App received 1,200+ downloads.

Education

2012-2016 Stratford University

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

- Redesigned the school's alumni fundraising site with .NET. Increased alumni use 30%.
- For senior project, trained 15 fellow students in ASP.NET MVC.

Skills

- **Soft skills:** Time management, interpersonal skills, teamwork, communication
- Hard skills: Programming, ASP.NET MVC, client-side web development, SQL

Activities

Developed .NET site for Salt Coast Animal Shelter. Increased donations 22%.

Avid surfer for fun and fitness.